{
  "Question1": [
    {
      "ID": "1",
      "Question" : "Which element has an atomic number 1 ?",
      "Answer" : "H"
    },
    {
      "ID": "2",
      "Question" : "Which element has an atomic number 2 ?",
      "Answer" : "He"
    },
    {
      "ID": "3",
      "Question" : "Which element has an atomic number 3 ?",
      "Answer" : "Li"
    },
    {
      "ID": "4",
      "Question" : "Which element has an atomic number 4 ?",
      "Answer" : "Be"
    },
    {
      "ID": "5",
      "Question" : "Which element has an atomic number 5 ?",
      "Answer" : "B"
    },
    {
      "ID": "6",
      "Question" : "Which element has an atomic number 6 ?",
      "Answer" : "C"
    },
    {
      "ID": "7",
      "Question" : "Which element has an atomic number 7 ?",
      "Answer" : "N"
    },
    {
      "ID": "8",
      "Question" : "Which element has an atomic number 8 ?",
      "Answer" : "O"
    },
    {
      "ID": "9",
      "Question" : "Which element has an atomic number 9 ?",
      "Answer" : "F"
    },
    {
      "ID": "10",
      "Question" : "Which element has an atomic number 10 ?",
      "Answer" : "Ne"
    }
  ]
}
